{
    "id": "1807a2ab91c644db9ac279c97a4c1ddf",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The tweezers must be in the cupboard ...................... the sink",
            "description": "Below and under can both mean ‘lower than’.",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "28558eca5f8e4b80a8858911a63a34a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "If she doesn’t come soon, we will ……………….. without her.",
            "description": "There is usually no difference between begin and start.",
            "answers": [
                "start",
                "begin",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "52eb8ce073b548af9f582d2ea0b096ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t like this shirt. ……………….., it is too expensive.",
            "description": "Besides can mean also. Beside means next to or at the side of.",
            "answers": [
                "Besides",
                "Beside",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "de055d94ddc94b6fac7af29a04b0eac9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is still ……………….. eighteen.",
            "description": "We use under to mean younger than.",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "below",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "642e4faf8d2d4851b6b4ca981d08ef17"
        },
        {
            "question": "A lot of businesses are going ……………… because of the economic crisis.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e712246c5d784cfab94d34a19a3c813e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I came up ………………… the magistrate for dangerous driving.",
            "description": "We use ‘before’ to mean ‘in the presence of somebody important’. ",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "in front of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "676188b894a04352a4749e86094a3c90"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I worked fast, I finished early.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction. We use it before a clause. Because of is a preposition. We use it before a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "Because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fb40aefde151447a9ff86edc4ff33391"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. 72 kilos.",
            "description": "Weigh is one of those verbs that are not used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "weighs",
                "is weighing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5b65e427def4d5e8d9c75ce7500aeda"
        },
        {
            "question": "As well as ………………… his arm, he hurt his leg.",
            "description": "When we put a verb after as well as, we most often use the –ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "breaking",
                "break",
                "he broke"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9041c9c1a85409d9dc733a11979dcf4"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can take my car …………………. you drive carefully.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on condition that",
                "as long as",
                "so long as",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "1f138ac13e714257ba538b72ad4cf136"
        },
        {
            "question": "The house ………………. I live is very small.",
            "description": "That cannot be used instead of where.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "89f6483125294cc29abc0785b5e6ffd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. a lot of interesting experiences during my year in Africa.",
            "description": "Experience is generally used with the verb have.",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "made",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "810ee7c6bed74fa9b45ea89cd073a566"
        }
    ]
}